Linnae J. Kraemer

linnaekraemer@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/linnae-kraemer 512-822-0855 github.com/LinnaeK

As a software engineer I solve real world problems through collaboration, logical frameworks, and attention to detail. I use my skills as an entrepreneur in the music industry to be proactive, manage time wisely, and always consider the users' experience. I have a passion for excellence and find joy in making the world a better place through the work that I do.

Professional Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS
- Javascript
- Jquery

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Python
- AngularJS
- NodeJS

- ReactJS
- Git
- Github
- Agile/Scrum
- Mongoose

Experience

General Assembly, Software Engineering Fellow

Oct 2019 - Present

- Three-month, 500-hour full-time and full-stack software engineering program.
- Multi-campus connected experience with the latest front- and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies
- Design and create word-based game using HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- Built and design full-stack music studio lesson and student tracker using Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, EJS, and Javascript.

Music Instructor 2004-Present

- Greater Austin Music Academy, Clavier-Werke South, String Project, University of Texas
- Through personal private music studio, taught 35+ harp and piano students music, technique, and music theory
- Provide systematic practice plans for each week and consistently evaluate progress in order to tailor presentation of materials
- Organize and conduct group ensembles for 6+ performances a year
- Prepare students for individual performances and competitions including All State, Regions, TMEA, and Sewannee Music Festival

Americorp Member, CitySquare

Jun 2012-Aug 2012

- Serve 100s of underprivileged children in the Austin metro area fresh lunches
- Engage the children in 30 minutes of physical activity through active outdoor games
- Develop personal relationships with the children during the weekly interactions

Education

General Assembly, Software Engineering Intensive

The University of Texas at Austin, Bachelor of Arts in Music, Harp, Computer Science focused minor